<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SL Recipes</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="reg_success">Registration success!</string>
    <string name="reg_fail">Registration failed!</string>
    <string name="no_internet">No Internet Connection!</string>
    <string name="pref_file">com.abc.preference_file</string>
    <string name="pref_login_status">com.abc.preference_login_status</string>
    <string name="pref_user_name">com.abc.preference_user_name</string>
    <string name="idUser"></string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_no_log_activity">NoLog_activity</string>
    <string name="network_error">network error</string>
    <string name="title_activity_logged">LoggedActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_log_activity">Log_activity</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">These terms and conditions (&quot;Terms&quot;, &quot;Agreement&quot;) are an agreement between Mobile Application Developer (&quot;Mobile Application Developer&quot;, &quot;us&quot;, &quot;we&quot; or &quot;our&quot;) and you (&quot;User&quot;, &quot;you&quot; or &quot;your&quot;). This Agreement sets forth the general terms and conditions of your use of the SL recipes mobile application and any of its products or services (collectively, &quot;Mobile Application&quot; or &quot;Services&quot;).\n
        \n
        Accounts and membership\n
        \n
        If you create an account in the Mobile Application, you are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with it. Providing false contact information of any kind may result in the termination of your account. You must immediately notify us of any unauthorized uses of your account or any other breaches of security. We will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions.\n
        \n
        User content\n
        \n
        We do not own any data, information or material (&quot;Content&quot;) that you submit in the Mobile Application in the course of using the Service. You shall have sole responsibility for the accuracy, quality, integrity, legality, reliability, appropriateness, and intellectual property ownership or right to use of all submitted Content. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor Content in the Mobile Application submitted or created using our Services by you. Unless specifically permitted by you, your use of the Mobile Application does not grant us the license to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish or distribute the Content created by you or stored in your user account for commercial, marketing or any similar purpose. But you grant us permission to access, copy, distribute, store, transmit, reformat, display and perform the Content of your user account solely as required for the purpose of providing the Services to you.\n
        \n
        Backups\n
        \n
        We perform regular backups of the  Content, however, these backups are for our own administrative purposes only and are in no way guaranteed. You are responsible for maintaining your own backups of your data. We do not provide any sort of compensation for lost or incomplete data in the event that backups do not function properly. We will do our best to ensure complete and accurate backups, but assume no responsibility for this duty.\n
        \n
        Changes and amendments\n
        \n
        We reserve the right to modify this Agreement or its policies relating to the Mobile Application or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement in the Mobile Application. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Continued use of the Mobile Application after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. Policy was created with https://www.WebsitePolicies.com\n
        \n
        Acceptance of these terms\n
        \n
        You acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Mobile Application or its Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to use or access the Mobile Application and its Services.\n
        \n
        Contacting us\n
        \n
        If you have any questions about this Agreement, please contact us.\n
        \n
        This document was last updated on February 14, 2019</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Cookies are small text files that can be used by websites to make a user\'s experience more efficient.\n
        \n
        The law states that we can store cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of this site. For all other types of cookies we need your permission.\n
        \n
        This site uses different types of cookies. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages.\n
        \n
        You can at any time change or withdraw your consent from the Cookie Declaration on our website.\n
        \n
        Learn more about who we are, how you can contact us and how we process personal data in our Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="contact">
        tel: +421 909 211 569\n
        \n
        email: sladmin@slrecipes.com
    </string>

</resources>
